I used four products from my's
pomegranate and honey collection let's
talk about it last month we did two
hairstyles as well as a watch day using
the shampoo conditioner twisting sule
and curl smoothie at first I thought the
shampoo and conditioner was nothing
really special and then after looking at
this footage bro I don't know they might
have cooked with this one cuz my hair
has never looked like this after just a
shampoo and condition the post wash was
a little different leaving my hair curly
but a little drier than it should be but
after using this curl smoothie to add
some definition and hydration to my hair
I found a quick solution which gave me
this beautiful curly fro as a result and
as for the twisting sule I'll be
completely honest with you yo I'll
probably never use this thing again I
use this product to do twist and this is
where the emotional roller coaster comes
in because at first my hair was super
hard and then once the cast broke it did
so in like a flurry of flakes I shook my
hair and stuff was just flying all over
the place it shrunk my hair up so much
even right now just with curls my hair
is past my eye my twist should not be up
here bro